Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 54394; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 videocassettes (vhs)
  - Remarks Re: the Effects of Reagan's Budget Cuts, Hearing of the Subcommittee on Post-Secondary Education (NYU), 1982-03-05; 55723 (Box 257, Folder 13)
  - Brademas Named "Man of the Year" by the Alpha Omega Council (Boston, MA), 1982-03-06; 55721 (Box 257, Folder 14)
  - Remarks Re: International Education, Mason and Sons Dedication Breakfast (NYU), 1982-03-07; 55719 (Box 257, Folder 15)
  - Remarks Re: Social Justice, to Group Involved in Social Work Education (NYU), 1982-03-07; 55720 (Box 257, Folder 16)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture -- Welcome Remarks (NYU), 1982-03-10; 55718 (Box 257, Folder 17)
  - Remarks Re: Outreach in Palm Beach, University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1982-03-11; 55717 (Box 257, Folder 18)
  - Remarks Re: Government Aid to Education, Luncheon Meeting of the NYU Finance Club (Two World Trade Center, NY), 1982-03-11; 55716 (Box 257, Folder 19)
  - "Does Public Education Have a Future?", School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions (SEHNAP) (NYU), 1982-03-13; 55715 (Box 257, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1982-03-15 (Box 257, Folder 21)
  - Public Interest Lecture, Cosmopolitan Club (New York, NY), 1982-03-15; 55714 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Institute Annual Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYU), 1982-03-18; 55712 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Talking Points Re: the Budget, Faculty Council (NYU), 1982-03-18; 55711 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Breakfast (NYU), 1982-03-21; 55710 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - American Education Research Association (New York Hilton, NY), 1982-03-22; 55709 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Remarks Re: the Reagan Budget Cuts, Dental College Sesquicentennial Dinner, 1982-03-22; 55708 (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Remarks Re: the Reagan Budget Cuts, NYU School of Medicine Faculty Meeting, 1982-03-23; 55707 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Remarks by Herbert Silverman, 150th Anniversary of the Dental Center, 1982-03-23; 55706 (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Remarks Re: the Study of Foreign Languages, the Friends of Greek Studies (Ball State University, Muncie, IN), 1982-03-24; 55704 (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Introductory Remarks to the Ninth Annual Stephen J. Brademas, Sr., Lecture at Ball State University (Muncie, IN), 1982-03-25; 55703 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Moskowitz Lecture (NYU), 1982-03-31; 55702 (Box 258, Folder 11)
  - Remarks Re: the Reagan Administration, Publishers Lunch Club (Yale Club), 1982-04-01; 55701 (Box 258, Folder 12)
  - Remarks Re: the Effect of Budget Cuts on Education, the Administrators' Roundtable (CUNY), 1982-04-02; 55700 (Box 258, Folder 13)
  - Remarks Re: Housing and Development, NYU Law School Faculty Meeting, 1982-04-05; 55699 (Box 258, Folder 14)
  - Reception for the Journal of International Law and Politics, 1982-04-02; 55698 (Box 258, Folder 15)
  - Lord Caradon Lecture (NYU), 1982-04-12; 55697 (Box 258, Folder 16)
  - Lord Briggs Lecture (NYU), 1982-04-14; 55696 (Box 258, Folder 17)
  - Remarks Re: Development and Housing, University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1982-04-15; 55695 (Box 258, Folder 18)
  - Remarks Re: the Effects of Budget Cuts by the Reagan Administration, Postgraduate and University Hospital Alumni Association Dinner, 1982-04-20; 55693 (Box 258, Folder 19)
  - Leo Jaffe Dinner (NYU), 1982-04-21; 55692 (Box 258, Folder 20)
  - Welcome Remarks Re: Nuclear Arms, David Kriser Seminar (NYU), 1982-04-22; 55691 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Founders Day Dinner and Convocation (NYU), 1982-04-22; 55689 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Citation Honoring Theodore M. Hesburg at Founders Day, 1982-04-22; 177020 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Address, 160th Commencement Exercises at the University of Pittsburgh, 1982-04-25; 55688 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Remarks Re: the Effects of Reagan Budget Cuts, School of Social Work Benefit (NYU Club), 1982-04-25; 55687 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Talking Points, "Effect of Public Policy on Human Development," Sunrise Semester, 1982-04-26; 55686 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Installation of Howard Squadron as President of the American Jewish Congress (with Ambassador Ghorbal of Egypt), 1982-04-28; 55684 (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - Remarks Re: Business and Education Technology, Association for a Better New York and American Jewish Community, 1982-04-28; 55685 (Box 259, Folder 8)
  - Remarks by Brademas and L. Jay Oliva, Italian Heritage and Culture Week Proclamation Ceremony (Washington Square Park, NY), 1982-04-30; 55682 (Box 259, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: the History of Experimental Education, Occasion of the Tenth Anniversary of NYU's Gallatin Division, 1982-04-30; 55683 (Box 259, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Central America and The Caribbean (NYU), 1982-05-02; 55680 (Box 259, Folder 11)
  - Talking Points Re: Financial Aid, Meeting with NYU Student Senators Council, 1982-05-06; 55678 (Box 259, Folder 12)
  - Remarks Re: Washington and Albany, University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1982-05-06; 55677 (Box 259, Folder 13)
  - Remarks Re: the Village, Caring Community Lunch (NYU), 1982-05-06; 55679 (Box 259, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1982-05-10 (Box 259, Folder 15)
  - Indiana University Commencement Address (South Bend, IN), 1982-05-11; 55675 (Box 259, Folder 16)
  - University of Southern California Commencement Address (Los Angeles, CA), 1982-05-13; 55674 (Box 259, Folder 17)
  - Talking Points Re: the School of Business and Public Administration, Meeting with the Marketing Society, 1982-05-18; 55673 (Box 259, Folder 18)
  - Japan International Christian University Foundation Luncheon (NYU), 1982-05-19 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin Fellows Dinner (NYU), 1982-05-19; 177021 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Auchincloss Dinner at Rockefeller University (New York, NY), 1982-05-19; 177022 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Talking Points Re: the Differences Between Indiana and Washington, D.C., Washington Square Association, 1982-05-20; 55670 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - NYU Faculty Council Luncheon, 1982-05-20; 55671 (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - Manchester College Commencement Address (North Manchester, IN), 1982-05-23; 55669 (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Huxley Convocation and Dinner (NYU Medical Center), 1982-05-24; 55668 (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - Governor Carey Receiving Weiler Award (Pierre Hotel, NY), 1982-05-25; 55667 (Box 260, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation Dinner (NYU), 1982-05-27; 55666 (Box 260, Folder 9)
  - NYU Medical School Commencement (Lincoln Center, NY), 1982-06-02; 55665 (Box 260, Folder 10)
  - The 34th Annual Business Conference, Rutgers University (New Brunswick, NJ), 1982-06-03; 55664 (Box 260, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Executive Committee Meeting, 1982-06-07 (Box 260, Folder 12)
  - Remarks Re: Financial Aid, Administrative Management Council (NYU), 1982-06-09; 55662 (Box 260, Folder 13)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner (NYU), 1982-06-09; 177023 (Box 260, Folder 14)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch at Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner (NYU), 1982-06-09 (Box 260, Folder 15)
  - 150th NYU Commencement, Script and Speeches (Washington Square Park, NY), 1982-06-10; 177024 (Box 261, Folder 1-2)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch, NYU Commencement, 1982-06-10; 55659 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Remarks by H.R. Silverman, NYU Commencement, 1982-06-10; 177026 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - Kalamazoo College Commencement Address (Kalamazoo, MI), 1982-06-12; 55656 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - DePaul University Commencement Address (Chicago, IL), 1982-06-13; 55655 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Remarks Re: International Education, Citizens Budget Commission International Urban Symposium (NYU), 1982-06-14; 55654 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - Remarks Re: Attributes for Being a Lawyer, National Association of College and University Attorneys (Waldorf Astoria Hotel, NY), 1982-07-08; 55653 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Remarks Re: U.S. Trade with Japan, Luncheon Meeting at the International House of Japan (Tokyo, Japan), 1982-07-13; 55652 (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - Seminar on U.S.-Japan Economic Relations, Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Aspen, CO), 1982-08-16; 55651 (Box 261, Folder 10)
  - Remarks Re: the Education Commission of the States, James Bryant Conant Award (Portland, OR), 1982-08-20; 55650 (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - Congress of the International Comparative Literature Association (NYU), 1982-08-23; 177027 (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - Academic Convocation for New Students (NYU), 1982-09-09; 55649 (Box 261, Folder 13)
  - Education Panel of the Biennial Conference of the National Italian American Foundation (Washington, D.C.), 1982-09-10; 55648 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - University of Richmond Opening Convocation (Richmond, VA), 1982-09-15; 55647 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meeting (NYU) (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Meeting with NYU Students, 1985-09-25; 55645 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Remarks Re: The Search for Democracy and Efficiency in American Government by Douglas Yates, 1982-09-27; 55644 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council (NYU), 1982-09-30; 55643 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon in Honor of Jorge Luis Borges (New York Institute for the Humanities, NYU), 1982-10-01; 55642 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - St. Francis of Assisi Eighth Centenary Celebration (NYU), 1982-10-05; 55641 (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Annual Dinner of the American Associates of Ben-Gurion University of the Negev (Pierre Hotel, NY), 1982-10-05; 55640 (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration / Tel Aviv University Reception (NYU), 1982-10-07; 55639 (Box 262, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner Honoring John Loeb (Waldorf Astoria, NY), 1982-10-07; 55638 (Box 262, Folder 11)
  - Interview on "Public Hearing" (Broadcast on WCBS), 1982-10-08; 55637 (Box 262, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Annual Alumni Awards Dinner (New York University Club), 1982-10-13; 55636 (Box 262, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1982-10-14; 55635 (Box 262, Folder 14)
  - Friends of Town Hall Award Dinner (New York University Club), 1982-10-17; 55634 (Box 262, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1982-10-18; 55633 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council (NYU), 1982-10-21; 55632 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Award Presented to Governor Carey, NYU Law School Alumni Day, 1982-10-23; 55631 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Parents Day (NYU), 1982-10-24; 55630 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Opening Session of the National Forum of the College Board (Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NY), 1982-10-27; 55629 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Fifth Avenue Association (Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NY), 1982-10-27; 55628 (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Dental Associates Dinner (St. Regis-Sheraton Hotel, NY), 1982-10-27; 55627 (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Ex-Cell-O Reception at the School of Graduate Business Administration (NYU), 1982-10-28; 177028 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Archbishop Iakovos High School Dinner (Jamaica, NY), 1982-10-29; 55626 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Greek High School Parents Conference, St. Demetrios High School (Astoria, NY), 1982-10-30; 55625 (Box 263, Folder 10)
  - Louis Marshall Memorial Dinner, Jewish Theological Seminary (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1982-10-31; 55624 (Box 263, Folder 11)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch and John Brademas, Tisch School of the Arts Faculty Convocation (NYU), 1982-11-01; 55623 (Box 263, Folder 12)
  - Council on International Education Exchange Annual Conference (NYU), 1982-11-03; 55622 (Box 263, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees of the Institute of Fine Arts Meeting (NYU), 1982-11-08; 55620 (Box 263, Folder 14)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Associates Dinner (St. Regis-Sheraton Hotel, NY), 1982-11-08; 55621 (Box 263, Folder 15)
  - "Pressure Group Attacks on Free Speech," 92nd St. Y and New York Civil Liberties Union, 1982-11-09; 55619 (Box 263, Folder 16)
  - NYU Alumnae Club Woman of Achievement Award, Presented to Grace Glueck (NYU), 1982-11-09; 55618 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council Meeting (NYU), 1982-11-10; 55617 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1982-11-11; 55616 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Remarks by L. Jay Oliva at NYU Alumni Association of Southern California (Los Angeles, CA), 1982-11-13; 55615 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - John Sessions Memorial Award Presentation (Robert Wagner Archives, NYU), 1982-11-17; 55614 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration of Jonathan Fanton as President of the New School (New York, NY), 1982-11-18; 55613 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - Remarks Re: Arthur T. Vanderbilt, Institute of Judicial Administration Dinner (Sheraton Centre Hotel, NY), 1982-11-18; 55612 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - Remarks Re: a Proposed Japanese Center at NYU, Keidanren Kaikan (Tokyo, Japan), 1982-11-22; 55611 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Japanese NYU Alumni Association Reception (Japan), 1982-11-22; 55610 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: Library Resources, Dean's Lunch Honoring Phillip Johnson and Richard Foster (NYU), 1982-11-29; 55608 (Box 264, Folder 10)
  - Foreword, Student Financial Aid Handbook, 1982-11-29; 55609 (Box 264, Folder 11)
  - Remarks Re: the Handicapped, Blum Presidential Citation (School of Education, NYU), 1982-12-01; 55607 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - Commerce Alumni Association Dean's Day (NYU), 1982-12-04; 55606 (Box 264, Folder 13)
  - Tribute to Reubin Seldin (NYU College of Dentistry), 1982-12-09; 177029 (Box 264, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting in Washington Square Park (New York, NY), 1982-12-09; 55605 (Box 264, Folder 15)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Broadway Preview (New York, NY), 1982-12-09; 55604 (Box 264, Folder 16)
  - Remarks by Dean David Oppenheim, Tisch School of the Arts Broadway Preview, 1982-12-09; 55603 (Box 264, Folder 17)
  - Memo to the Domestic Policy Study Group Center for National Policy, 1982-12-10; 55602 (Box 264, Folder 18)
  - Remarks Re: Dr. Fritz Machlup, Department of Economics Reception (NYU), 1982-12-14; 55601 (Box 264, Folder 19)
  - Reception for Leon Shimkin (NYU), 1982-12-14; 55600 (Box 264, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council (NYU), 1982-12-16; 55599 (Box 264, Folder 21)
  - Review of Congress and the Common Good, by Arthur Maas, 1983; 177030 (Box 264, Folder 22)
  - 35th Anniversary of the Fulbright Program in Greece (Athens, Greece), 1983-01-12; 55596 (Box 264, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Council Executive Management Training in Athens Program (Athens, Greece), 1983-01-13; 55594 (Box 264, Folder 24)
  - Remarks by Brademas and Laurence Tisch, Federal Reserve Bank of New York Dinner (Regency Hotel, NY), 1983-01-19; 55590 (Box 264, Folder 25)
  - New York Federal Executive Board (Vista Hotel, World Trade Center, NY), 1983-01-19; 55593 (Box 264, Folder 26)
  - Radio Interview Re: the Education Commission (WCBS), 1983-01-19; 55592 (Box 264, Folder 27)
  - Humphrey Award, Metropolitan Social Studies Conference (New York Hilton, NY), 1983-01-22; 55589 (Box 264, Folder 28)
  - Presidential Citation Dinner for Robert Badinter (NYU), 1983-01-22; 55588 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Universal Studios Luncheon Honoring John Brademas (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-27; 55587 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Remarks by Preston R. Tisch, Luncheon Honoring John Brademas (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-27; 55586 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Southern California Association for Philanthropy (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-28; 55585 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors Meeting (NYU Club), 1983-02-01; 55584 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Statement on Draft Registration and Student Aid (NYU), 1983-02-02; 55583 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon to Introduce Alan Altschuler, Graduate School of Public Administration (NYU), 1983-02-03; 55582 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meeting, 1983-02-07 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-02-10; 55580 (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Touche Ross Roundtable on the Management of Higher Education (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1983-02-14; 55579 (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council Meeting (NYU), 1983-02-15; 55578 (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Talking Points Re: Claude Montana and Bergdorf Benefit for the Grey Art Gallery, 1983-02-15; 55577 (Box 265, Folder 12)
  - Press Conference on the Return of Men's Varsity Basketball at NYU, 1983-02-17; 55576 (Box 265, Folder 13)
  - Diane Belfer Luncheon (Palm Beach, FL), 1983-02-20; 55575 (Box 265, Folder 14)
  - Dinner Honoring Dean Stedman (NYU), 1983-02-04; 55574 (Box 265, Folder 15)
  - LBJ Symposium Commemorating FDR's 50th Anniversary (University of Texas), 1983-03-04; 55573 (Box 265, Folder 16)
  - Gallatin Vice-Chairmen and Dean's Breakfast (NYU), 1983-03-07; 55572 (Box 265, Folder 17)
  - Cunningham Dance Foundation Arts and Salute Dinner (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1983-03-07; 55571 (Box 265, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon Announcing New Development Campaign (NYU), 1983-03-08; 55570 (Box 265, Folder 19)
  - Remarks by Naomi Levine, John Brademas, George Heyman, and Laurence Tisch at Press Conference Announcing New Fundraising Campaign, 1983-03-08; 55569 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-03-10; 55566 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Introduction of Alexander Haig Public Policy Lecture (NYU), 1983-03-10; 55565 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Higher Education Conference (Washington, D.C.), 1983-03-11; 55564 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-03-14 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - War, Peace, and the News Media Conference (NYU), 1983-03-18; 55562 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Conference of Graduate School of Business Administration Alumni (NYU), 1983-03-19; 55561 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Launch for Catalan Week at NYU, 1983-03-21; 55560 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Dedication of the Kaplan Cancer Center (NYU Medical Center), 1983-03-22; 55559 (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: Fundraising, Inauguration of the Dental Center Ambassador Program, 1983-03-24; 55705 (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - Dinner for Alan Altshuler (NYU), 1983-03-24; 55558 (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - Colloquium on Catalonia in Modern Spain, 1983-03-24; 177031 (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - City Club of New York Luncheon, CUNY Graduate Center (New York, NY), 1983-03-25; 55556 (Box 266, Folder 13)
  - Archons of the Ecumenical Patriarchate Annual Banquet (Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NY), 1983-03-26; 55555 (Box 266, Folder 14)
  - Reception for Professor Gay Wilson Allen (NYU), 1983-04-04; 55554 (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Lubin Memorial Service, 1983-04-07; 55553 (Box 266, Folder 16)
  - Rabbi Morris Lieberman Memorial Lecture, Baltimore Hebrew Congregation (Baltimore, MD), 1983-04-23; 55551 (Box 266, Folder 17)
  - Recording for the Blind Awards (Yale Club), 1983-04-27; 55550 (Box 266, Folder 18)
  - Giscard d'Estaing Lecture and Dinner (NYU), 1983-04-27; 55549 (Box 266, Folder 19)
  - Great Teacher Awards (NYU), 1983-04-28; 55548 (Box 266, Folder 20)
  - "Sailing Against the Wind," Boston University Conference on Arts and Education, 1983-04-29; 55547 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-05; 55546 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Testimony by James C. Finlay Before the Higher Education Commission (New York State Assembly), 1983-05-06; 55545 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - "Public and Private Sectors," Graduate School of Public Administration Alumni Association (NYU), 1983-05-09; 55544 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-09 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Herbert H. Lehman Award Given to Martin Lipton, American Jewish Committee Dinner (New York, NY), 1983-05-10; 55542 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York (New York, NY), 1983-05-10; 55541 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - "Engaging a Whole World: The Humanities in the 1980s," The President's Forum at Claremont University (Claremont, CA), 1983-05-13; 55540 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Claremont Graduate School Commencement Address (Claremont, CA), 1983-05-14; 55539 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Dinner Honoring Dean Daniel Griffiths (NYU Club), 1983-05-20; 55538 (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Albany Commencement Address (Albany, NY), 1983-05-22; 55535 (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of the Third Floor (Bobst Library), 1983-05-23; 55534 (Box 267, Folder 12)
  - Annual Alumni Dinner (NYU Club), 1983-05-24; 55533 (Box 267, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee on Labor, Health and Human Services, U.S. House of Representatives (Washington, D.C.), 1983-05-24; 177032 (Box 267, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-31 (Box 267, Folder 15)
  - Pre-Commencement Dinner for the Board of Trustees (NYU), 1983-06-02; 55531 (Box 267, Folder 16)
  - School of Medicine Commencement (NYU), 1983-06-02; 55530 (Box 267, Folder 17)
  - NYU All-University Commencement, 1983-06-03; 55529 (Box 267, Folder 18)
  - University of Massachusetts Lowell Commencement Address (Lowell, MA), 1983-06-04; 55528 (Box 267, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Regional Conference of National State Budget Officers (Albany, NY), 1983-06-07; 55527 (Box 267, Folder 20)
  - Introductory Remarks for Claiborne Pell, American Council on the Arts Board Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1983-06-09; 55525 (Box 267, Folder 21)
  - Meeting of the Congressional Intern Program (Washington, D.C.), 1983-06-09; 55524 (Box 267, Folder 22)
  - Shady Side Academy Commencement Address (Pittsburgh, PA), 1983-06-10; 177033 (Box 267, Folder 23)
  - Dinner Honoring Reverend Boardman W. Kathan (NYU), 1983-06-14; 55522 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Life Gallatin Reception (NYU), 1983-06-14; 55521 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Induction Dinner of Dental School's Omega Chapter of Omicron Kappa Upsilon (New York, NY), 1983-06-15; 55520 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Introduction to Duel for the Dunes, by Norma Schaeffer and Kay Franklin, 1983-06-23; 55519 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Fifth National Conference on Communications Technology in Education and Training, 1983-06-27; 55518 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Birkbeck College, University of London (London, England), 1983-06-30; 55517 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Foreword to Lifelong Learning Leaders Retreat Report, 1983-07-01; 55516 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Chapter on International Education in U.S., 1983-07-07; 55512 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - Talking Points for Graduate Education Hearing, National Commission on Student Financial Assistance, 1983-07-07; 177034 (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - French-American Foundation Dinner (New York, NY), 1983-07-18; 177035 (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - NYU-High School for the Humanities Project Press Conference and Reception (NYU), 1983-07-25; 177036 (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Annual Meeting (San Antonio, TX), 1983-08-09; 177037 (Box 268, Folder 12)
  - New York Times Article Draft, 1983-08-12; 177038 (Box 268, Folder 13)
  - Design Magazine Article, 1983-08-15; 177039 (Box 268, Folder 14)
  - Written Piece for Cooper-Hewitt Museum Publication, 1983-09-01 (Box 268, Folder 15)
  - Speech Re: the Kennedy Assassination, 1983-09-02; 177040 (Box 268, Folder 16)
  - Student Convocation (NYU), 1983-09-12; 177041 (Box 268, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-09-14 (Box 268, Folder 18)
  - BobCat Press Conference, 1983-09-15; 177043 (Box 268, Folder 19)
  - Montclair State College 75th Anniversary (Montclair, NJ), 1983-09-20; 177044 (Box 268, Folder 20)
  - Inaugural Symposium of the Indiana University Instititute for Advanced Study (Bloomington, IN), 1983-09-26; 177045 (Box 268, Folder 21)
  - All-University Graduate Student Reception (NYU), 1983-09-28; 177046 (Box 268, Folder 22)
  - Stephen Chan House Press Conference (Institute of Fine Art), 1983-09-29; 177047 (Box 268, Folder 23)
  - Stephen Chan House Dedication Ceremonies (Institute of Fine Art), 1983-09-30; 177048 (Box 268, Folder 24)